Yumi's song, isn't it low? At the beginning of the first song.
Well, well, well.
Yes, it is.
Suddenly it's higher.
Higher than anyone else's.
Suddenly it goes higher.
Indeed.
Yes. I look forward to working with you.
Hello!
Suddenly!
Yoo-hoo!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
This week, I've just started my shift.
It's GYOZA POND.
Please come.
Yoo-hoo!
Surprisingly, it's been a while since I had a part-time job at GYOZA POND.
That's right.
We used to see each other frequently at events and so on.
I think I came here for the last time before New Year's Eve.
What?
Is that possible?
Of course it does.
When was the last time?
Was it before the end of the year?
Around November 30th.
That's not right.
Not even close.
It was taken before New Year's. Oh, right, right, right.
Thank you for the smile. You did it!
I've been waiting for BGP... BGP
Yosapan, hi!
Master is here. He's Bob.
He's not Bob, though.
Yes, it is.
It got a little too shaggy.
I had to cut it off.
You got the ends right.
It's nice. The short cut is very well received. Yes, it's very well received.
Thank you very much. You are irresistible! When I walk around town, everyone looks back at me when I walk like this, and that's what happens.
That's what happens. I hope they do.
Is this the first time you've made it short, then? Yes, it is. Suddenly in Daikanai Devil. Yes, yes, I was surprised.
When I left without giving any notice, the audience was.
Yes, indeed. They were like, "Who is that guy? They were like, "Who is that guy?
We were surprised too. They didn't notice us.
First of all, did I do something wrong in the opening of the lecture? I didn't do anything wrong.
You know, you have a tendency to go for the easy way out, don't you? Yes, yes, yes.
No, I didn't. A change of scenery.
That's not what I meant. Well, this week, we're going to start recording again. I would like to start the recording for Thursday, May 11.
Please watch it with a warm eye. Please keep a warm eye on us. Yes, I will. Please do.
So, yesterday, Sugawara...
One more time? One more time. I bit it, so I'll go one more time.
Yesterday, YESTERDAY, was amazing!
The whole town was jammed with cars for my birthday!
They were doing outside volleyball, right?
It was great, me, outside volleyball!
I was in some kind of bulletproof acrylic thing, looking this way and that.
Oh, my God!
Bulletproof!
Yokohama City was in an uproar.
It was a big mess, especially overseas.
But today is the 11th of May, so let's forget all about the mayhem for a moment.
First of all, let me tell you what day it is.
What day is tomorrow? The 11th will soon be over, and tomorrow, May 12th...
What day is it?
This is, uh... Oh, my gosh! Crawfish Day!
Well, on May 12, 1927.
American crayfish were brought from America by a farmer in Kanagawa Prefecture.
That's quite a while ago. Almost 100 years ago.
It's been almost 100 years.
American crayfish were originally brought back to feed the edible cow frogs.
When they came here from America, there were only about 20 American crayfish.
But after that, they thrived, and the American crayfish was amazing.
Their fertility, their vitality, their life force...
I want to do it!
It's an instinctive way of life.
Yes, I know. They're not indigenous to Japan.
Cows were there as food back then, and they're still there now and then.
Have you ever eaten them? No, I've never had it. Not even with insects.
I ate it once when I was a kid.
Some kind of fried food? I didn't feel the frog feeling at all. It was rather delicious. It's the same as chicken. You'd never know if you weren't told.
Are you being set up? Are you being lied to? Are you okay? No, no, I'm fine. - Really? Sometimes I eat it like a leg on purpose, but you can't really tell.
Sometimes they do it on purpose to make it look like a foot or something.
But I could eat it normally. So, at that time, this kind of food was very precious to me. It was still in the second year of the Showa era (1927), before the war.
I see. That's why I think that cow frogs were a good source of animal protein. I'm really good at croaking cow frogs.
What? Well, you know what?
Boo! What the hell is wrong with you? You don't sound anything like him! I don't know what the real one looks like!
I'm like, "What? What? It's really a cow!
It's a cow. It used to be better.
It was better about 10 years ago.
A bit of a blank. Really?A little blank. Really?
It wasn't like that.
It wasn't like that. I think it was more like... well, a little bit.
I guess so. I think there are a lot of people who say they look like it. Is it true?
They say it's delicious. That's amazing.
I can't believe you yawned during the recording. What's that?
No, it's not!
Uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh. You look like him! It's just like him!
I remember!
Uh-oh. Oh, yeah!
Are you sick from drinking too much? Ew! You idiot!
Your comments are so depressing! I'm being tortured!
Everyone really likes to make fun of me. It's called "making fun of me.
It's called "comic relief." You know, when you make fun of someone and they make fun of you.
I mean, the cow guide was with the American crayfish, too.
And they also attack and eat the Japanese native species.
I see... By the way... American crabs are, of course...
We thought they were red back then.
We fished and caught crabs, didn't we? Yes, we did.
Did you also go to the dumpling place? Yes, in school.
Like American crayfish fishing? I don't know if it was American crayfish or not, but there was crayfish fishing. Japanese crayfish are not red at all.
They are light brown, not that big. Like makkachin.
They are tiny. They are a little small.
Are they really in the rice paddies? Yes, yes, yes, in the rice paddies, in beautiful places.
Like a river.
I used to catch them in elementary school.
We had a string attached to the end of a tree branch.
Like a hooked squid or something.
If you tie it like this, it'll eat you up fast.
And they don't let go. That's right.
I caught more and more. I miss it.
It brings back memories.
When we were in elementary school, "makkachin" was all the rage.
I used to bring them home and put them in my aquarium.
The truth is, I'm told that even the original American Zaligar ran away.
These guys are amazing.
I don't know if they jump or what.
I don't know if they're jumping or what, but they're pretty high up, and this is the size of the tank.
I don't know how they got out.
I don't know how they got out, but they were gone, like, the next day.
They don't leave.
I don't know.
I think it was like this... like a "ping"... which is impossible, because... that's right.
He ran away on his own somewhere in the house.
The next day, I was going to school, and when I tried to put on my shoes, he said, "Jalie.
What? I looked at my shoes and saw Makatin in them.
Oh my God!
I don't know if he can jump that high, but...
I don't know if he can jump that high or not... but his American blood... USA blood...
It's not easy to get through.
The scissors are very powerful, too.
Don't underestimate it, or you'll get hit.
I didn't touch it. You didn't touch it?
I was scared.
I was scared... I mean, I'm used to seeing crayfish and shrimp, but...
But when you turn them inside out, they look like this.
You can't touch them... if you grab them by the neck.
You can hold the scissors by the base of the scissors, like this.
That's great!
And then you touch your friend's face or something... Oh no, that's a cut on the mouth.
It's easy to do. Put them in the hood of your hoodie.
The whole class, he just acted like he didn't know what was going on
Like that.
Like an idiot. Well, well, well. That's why I'm here. Okay, then, let's hear from you. Let's hear from you all.
Let's see, first of all...
I got a nice picture.
I got it. This is Mr. Mineral. Thank you very much. He often sends me his drawings, and they are very nice and full of love.
It is a very nice picture, full of love.
I drew Master and Rhea. Thank you very much. It looks like this.
Amazing raining It's pretty bad, isn't it?
I like the shading.
I like baldness so much.
I love baldness so much, and I'm 100 times better at it than you are.
I'm surprised to find out that I've been turned into something better than my a!
Boo hoo!
I'm not sure if it was written by the same person or not, but it's art...
It's like, "Oh, my God, I'm me, I'm me, I'm me, I'm me, I'm me, I'm me...
I'm not sure if this is the same thing as this or that.
It's so cute! You really drew last week's outfit!
I can't describe it. It's like you painted it three-dimensionally.
It's amazing. Do you have a technique?
But I guess that's what you get when you really balance light and shadow.
I don't know. I don't know either.
It's a great shade, but I don't think it's a question of light or that sarpon.
It's not about shading. Shading has nothing to do with it.
I don't care about the shading.
Can you please answer my question? Thank you, Mr. Sagamihara.
You're an office worker.
Good evening, Master Araya and Mr. Ebijubite. I always enjoy watching your work.
The other day, a bud appeared on the grapevine in our yard.
I'd like to send you a picture of the buds that appeared on the grapevine in our yard the other day.I'm sending you a photo of the buds that have formed. When the fruit starts to change color, you can eat them.
Most of them are eaten by birds!
I planted them when I was in elementary school and they have grown with me for over 40 years, so I am very attached to them.
I'm worried about the quality of the picture because it was taken with a long old smartphone, but I hope you can see it.
Yes, so this is what it looks like. Wow, it's a grape, a leaf. This one, this one, this one, this one. And then, this one is growing into a grape.
Wow, that's amazing. Like this. Oh, I see. It's so tiny at first. I've never seen it before.
Like grapevines. I see. Wow, that's nice. Birds eat them, don't they? Yes, they eat them. Birds are hungry, too. That's right. After all, they are alive.
When I was walking around, if I bought a standing-only noodle shop, I would eat it right away, right?
It's just like that.
Maybe it's just like that.
I'm getting better and better.
Grapes must be delicious.
Yes, they are.
They are good.
Oh, and one more thing,
What a surprise, a photo from a dumpling fan.
Oh, yes.
Is this okay, then?
Okay, like this. I don't think the live audience will understand the meaning of this. I'm sure you don't understand the meaning of this. This is it.
This is mugwort bread. This is mugwort bread. Actually, I like mugwort bread the best among breads.
But recently, I have been eating bread less often because I have been thinking that rice is more suitable for Japanese people. What?
I really wanted to eat it, so I went to an all-you-can-eat bread restaurant and then to a bakery,
I only eat what I like, medieval-style. I only ate the mugwort bread even though it was all-you-can-eat. I see.
And I was so happy that I took it. I see.
Mugwort grows very close to us. It grows on riverbanks.
That's right. That's right. There are so many of them.
So you can pick them yourself, cut them, and they are just as they are. That's right.
They're Western-style potatoes, so it's really amazing. It's delicious, and it's the best bread. But I was a little surprised for a moment. Why?
Because I like gyoza and bread, that's why it's called gyoza bread. Oh, I see. If you stop bread, does that mean you become ready-made gyoza bread?
No, no, we didn't. You've come back to it. I've reduced the frequency of eating. It's impossible for me not to eat completely, because my body can't accept it anymore.
I reduced it a little, but as a result of that reduction, I had an explosion of food. I still want to eat it.
I eat a lot of bread. I never ate a lot to begin with.
It's a habit. I wonder what it is. What is it that makes you so attached to dumpling buns? But my mom likes bread, too.
She herself gets itchy if she doesn't eat bread in a day.
Oh, that much?
She had to eat so much that it made her restless, and because she was brought up in that process, bread was in her short term.
It's in their DNA.
We have a lot of bread in the house, so of course we eat rice, too.
By the way, the Kobayashi family, the gyoza bread family.
For example, let's say the gyoza bread family is at home all day when they are off work.
They eat breakfast, lunch, and dinner during the day.
Are you like bread bread bread quite often?
I definitely eat bread in the morning.
Bread in the morning.
When breakfast was served, I was really like a little kid.
Wow, so it's breakfast.
Breakfast.
Lunch?
Sometimes it's lunch.
Dinner?
I get hungry at night.
But if I didn't have bread for breakfast or lunch, I have bread.
I've never had an experience that I end up with bread at night in my life. Sometimes it's bread in the morning at a hotel.
How about the Nakajima family, if you spend the whole day there?
I'm more of a bread person, so I ask for bread in the morning.
Is it because of the age of the family? What do you think?
Bread may not have been so popular in the Showa period.
But when I started eating rice, my body felt much better.
I felt lighter with rice.
I was really hungry, wasn't I?
But I still want to eat bread, and when I do, wow!
I want to taste that feeling, like I want to eat pork ramen.
That's right, that's right. I think that's what it was like.
I see... by the way, let's say it wasn't bread.
What does your mom cook for you? Like her specialty.
Keema curry and taco rice... but I'd make Grandpa's request and he'd say "that's great.
But I often say I'd like to eat gyoza, but other than that... well... takoyaki and keema curry...
Taco rice... That's right...
Okinawan style? Yes. There's lettuce, minced meat, and tomatoes.
My mom makes it for me. She laughed so hard. What's a gyoza mom? What's a gyoza mom?
She's a pretty good cook. I didn't say she's good at it. She doesn't say it herself, but it's delicious.
That's nice. That's the kind of mother I like.
Gyoza bread mummy.
By the way, is your mother in Nakajima Prefecture also a very good cook?
Yes, she is. Quite a lot. But she likes to cook.
I like my mother's cooking for Christmas and other celebrations.
She used lamb, like Spira ribs.
What's that?
She makes a kind of grilled dish. It's so delicious. We don't have lamb at home.
Like at Christmas time. Is Christmas really that big of a deal? NakajimaWe take Christmas very seriously at home.
Yes, we do.
From what I've heard, the Nakajima family has a pretty high level of economy.
The Nakajima family has a high level of economy. I thought so.
There are some things that come up in the conversation that I have no idea about. Do you see it?
Yes, I was surprised the other day. What was it? What was it, glamping? Oh, glamping.
You know what glamping is? I've heard of it. Do you know what it is?
It's that thing, you know, the camping thing. It's a camping kind of thing.
Do you know what glamping is?
You know, the kind where you stop and leak? You go to a place like a mountain.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, that's right. Well, it's a little bit like... what do you call it, a fashionable version of camping.
Yes, yes, I mean, a little bit of camping, a fashionable version of that, yes.
I don't understand.
I don't know what "glamping" means.
We were asking each other at the same time what glamping was... and then we were like, "Bokan!
But we went for the first time the other day, and it looked totally awesome... they had this huge seafood grill, and they were grilling these huge prawns...
Poor guy.
I bet he would've loved to swim in the sea.
No, they didn't just eejit them, they grilled them.
Put yourself in their shoes. They won't be able to eat anything.
Oh well... Mother!
My mom! No, no, no, no, no, no.
So, serve them.
Now that we're talking about bread, there's one more thing.
This is the melon bread we ordered for the show.
Hiroshima's melon bread, shaped like a rugby ball.
Have you heard of it? I think I've seen it before, but I've never had it.
And they were on a TV program, and they said that in western Japan, melon bread is basically like a rugby ball.
I've just received a letter saying that I didn't know that.
Former Meguro-ku, Chi-chan from Yamaguchi Prefecture, thank you very much!
Thank you, Master!
Yes, Ebichu, Mr. Ponkotsu-something!
The other day, you ordered a melon bread with custard from Hiroshima, but in neighboring Yamaguchi Prefecture, there is a melon bread with white bean paste in the shape of a rugby ball!
In the western part of Japan, these rugby ball shaped melon breads are called melon breads, and they are round and made of a kind of cookie!
The one covered with cookie dough is a bit sweeter, and is called "Sunrise"!
Cool! Well, well, well... the shape is a little bit different from the one I had the other day...
It's just like this! It was like a rugby ball!
Melon Pan is not melon bread because it looks like a melon.
No! It's not like that either.
I wonder where it comes from... I'm sure my mom bought it at a local supermarket when I was in elementary school, probably in the early days of melon bread.
It had a kind of smooth, kind of yellowish top, and I wonder what it was like to be so slippery.
It looked like melon fumiya, but when I opened it up, it was almost completely covered with a coating.
It's got a little coating on the top, but it's melon-y, and there's just raisins inside.
It was delicious. - Really?
I don't remember much, but my mom used to get really excited when she'd see these melon breads on sale at a discount.
She's kind of a picky eater.
I had a younger brother, but we were a family of men, and everyone was hungry, so they didn't care what it tasted like.
They didn't care what it tasted like.
Boom! Raisins!
Boom! Smoke! You recognized the smoke. That's about the extent of it.
Nowadays, melon bread is really, really good.
I guess the melon bread back then was just as good.
It's evolved, hasn't it?
Anyway, I think that bread has improved dramatically in the last 10 years or so.
I really can't get enough of this gyoza bread!
I mean, I can't switch to a life of rice.
I see.
Ordinary bread is so good!
I don't know.
It's really good! It's really good! It doesn't need anything! Steam it and eat it!
I've been to a show once before, but I don't like that kind of soft bread.
I don't like it when it's soft and chewy, especially with the soft and fluffy breads we're getting nowadays.
I don't like it. That's why I grab it like this.
Squeeze it hard and then drink it!
Compress it and make it hard before you drink it! I'm sure it tastes good.
I think it's not as good as it should be.
The baker worked so hard to make it soft and fluffy.
But I have my own tastes.
If it's not hard, it's not hard.
I'm sure there are some of you out there. I'm sure I'm one of them.
I have an announcement here.
LOL-chan's event, right?
I'm going to be a guest shell at LOL-chan's event on May 6th, which is a free event, so please be sure to attend.
I heard that there is an additional application for the second round of applications on the website starting April 29th.
If you register, you can take a look at it on the day of the event.
I hope you all can come to the event on Saturday, May 6th.
Please come!
So, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up?
By the way, for those of you who are on live TV, we've been recording all week, and there's never been so much going on as there has been this week.
I don't know what to say, I don't know what I did, but anyway, a lot of things happened.
So, all right, Tianjin people, see you next week, next week at about 8:00 p.m.
No?
Next week? Yes, next week.
Yes, there is!
Yes, there is. Well, well, well...
See you next week.
Let's hear one last word from Gyoza bread.
Yes, please. Eat bread, everyone! Bye!
Thank you. I know many of you are on fire right now.
Eat! I'll eat it when you say "eat it".
I'm going away.